One of those changes, of course, Malcolm Marks missing out through injury.
So Bongi and Banami comes in at Hooker.
A couple of heavy bookends with him in the shape of Franz Mahalba and Stephen Kitsoff.
Kitsoff on his way to Ireland.
Irish side Elster after the Rugby World Cup.
An experienced second row coming up with 200 counts between them.
There's the best on one you just hate to play against.
And of course alongside in Franco Moster.
The back row of Visa, Dutoy and Calisi.
Visa, a ferocious carrier.
Dutoy, he was just everywhere in round one and even got a try for himself.
And Calisi, the absolute poster boy of Rugby and its values.
Nine in ten, the Ever Eye catching fath the clerk.
He'll be serving Marnie LeBoc.
Publicly backed by a skipper recently.
He's no looking game one.
Possibly my favourite moment of the World Cup so far.
Damian, DLND and Jesse Creel.
DLND used to play for Ireland in Munster.
So he'll be well aware of what's to come for him.
And the back jury, Olympian Colby and one wing.
Aronser on the other.
The bull's speed start.
One of the best finishes in World Rugby.
And Vilumster, the powerful yet graceful man in the 15th shirt.
Coming as a six-stage grandson.
Winners they'd love to be champs of Europe and the world.
It's an all-enster front row with Andrew Porter,
Ronan Kellhart, and Ty Kvalon, the rugby world rugby dream team.
Two years in a row.
He's up for a great battle with Kitsoff as he'll face down in him in the scrum.
The Munster man, Ty Kvalon lines up alongside James Ryan.
He's captain of his country but it's his leadership at the line-out time.
Which could be crucial against the Africa.
And talking on leadership.
He goes out alongside Ireland players for the year for the 23rd calendar.
And Josh Fander-Flyer.
Nine-ten, the ever-exciting Pacie.
Jamie Gibson Park.
And then Flyhalf, Johnny Sexton.
Who has a thousand and ninety points to his name.
World record.
A center partnership by Andy Akir and Gary Ringrose.
They have 18 out of 22 wins when those two have played alongside each other.
And the big boot, James Lowe.
And the wing.
Kiu Akir continues to make the 15th in Jersey as well.
And Mac Hanson at 14, who said,
is probably everything he dream of growing up playing in games like this.
And then Dan Chin will make his work of World Cup debut.
If he comes up the bench.
Locking horns with the spring box.
And start the front.
So the Africa have fun memories from watching those that can't be fooled.
And winning the rugby world number one in the world Ireland.
Take on the defending champion South Africa.
It's a pull B match, which could easily be as tight as a facelift.
Welcome to start the front.
Straight away.
It's St. Louis.
Into the fray.
He's up in it.
South Africa.
And they're white, Jersey.
Their third strip of this rugby welcome.
Buff the clock.
They can go wide early on.
And it's been spilled on that side.
In the hole of the last rugby welcome.
To the front.
They go.
Tiger and Clon pinch.
Let's move downfield.
Backhand by Colby.
Not out.
Left behind.
From Mac Hanson.
Oh, it's gone backwards in the touch.
Happy new to meet.
And so I'm going to go cookie.
Buff the clock.
Spots a bit of space.
And it's an awkward bounce.
But it's good for South Africa.
Curly Anderson has it.
Look out.
Creel's on the inside.
Big Jesse Creel into the 22.
And a cleanup from DL Andy.
Through the legs it goes.
Seven style play there from Buff the clock.
Game back on.
Just for Vissa.
South Africa now.
They chose to attack.
Big step.
Dang it.
Bones up.
Does one side the twigs.
One in the box turns.
The flights go up.
South Africa have the opening points in this game.
They lost time.
They've beaten the Irish.
Bones up.
Rolls it backwards.
Aki again.
Burst to the line.
Bundi Aki looking to go in the halfway line.
Aki.
Is a sensation in this game.
Into the 22.
For Ireland.
Gibson Park.
So a bunch of watchers he's flying up on the right inside.
The right side.
Numbers to the left.
Porter.
For Ireland.
Can they capitalize on their break by Bundi Aki?
He carries again.
Delayed ball.
You know how many he's there.
Much better from this Irish side.
A second carry again from Andrew Porter.
David in 2017.
Sexton crunched as he gives the inside ball to James Lowe.
Porter for the third time.
The hits keep coming.
I don't know.
Gibson Park.
Shifts up to the right.
As Ireland.
Trying to make some progress here in the 22.
Sexton.
Rolling white Jews.
With the toy again.
Behind the back ball.
Trying to unlock.
Josh Vanderfield.
Sexton.
Over the topic goes.
Bundi Aki.
Bambiaki yet again, beautiful ball to low on the inside, needs help.
There's monsters all over it.
And a advantage for the Irish side.
Quarter.
Nice tummy from the front ball.
And then step.
A free play over the Irish side with advantage.
Gifts and pawns.
Still got a penalty advantage.
Across they'll go.
The cross kick.
Wrong hand short.
And Ireland will come by.
You're always in contact.
Do the tech left.
Goes to ground.
No clear release.
That is great news for the Irish side.
They're crowded.
Love the kick for the corner.
Because here comes Canada now.
To the front.
Thunderflip.
Peels around.
It's a bad hasn't.
Bambiaki.
Their most dangerous runner tonight.
Still the Irish wave comes.
Outside Africa.
Gifts and pawn to the right.
Forward's quickly re-gathering themselves for the next wave.
If you don't have many.
Gifts and pawn.
Looks both ways.
Again it's Thunderflip.
Ireland inching the way close up to the springback.
Beautiful play.
Sexton throws it.
He gets so close.
Here it is.
Hands behind.
To the right.
Lower the numbers there.
Ireland will score.
And they put it down.
Mac Hansen.
Rubged one in for the Irish.
And the crowd are rough.
Why it's a beautiful bit of play, Johnny Sexton gets so close, the scramble from South
Korea.
And it goes wide into the hands of the Mastasio at Mac Hansen, who gets over for Ireland's
first score, seven points if Sexton can put this one over.
What a moment for Mac Hansen, born and bred in Canberra, Australia, played super rugby
for the Brombies, was actually can be.
There are too many other titles to list right now, as he lines up the extra two, does Sexton.
It's straight through the middle, it's Ireland's seven, so that's an apricot three there.
Just to skip out, just with this up, gets him par, Sexton quick hands.
Time for long, the extra ball is there.
James Ryan catches forward.
Ireland back to the step to tour, has it?
Oh, difficult pass for a police to take.
Oh my gosh.
My bio just half time.
Ireland coming through, yeah.
And that is the first 40 minutes gone.
You're insane.
Denny North of Paris.
It's the pull B battle at the 2023 Rugby World Cup.
When you'd be closer, it is.
A half done score.
Seas Ireland leads to Liverpool 7-3.
Looks on from Ireland.
You're watching the second half between Ireland and South Africa.
From stunning start to France.
At the 2023 Rugby World Cup, Ireland on the left, lead.
7-3 against South Africa.
Andy Acki with a take.
Welcome to you for the thrilling pull B matchup.
I'm down the staff with pitch side net.
You need to use your own side.
Great.
Good time, Mitch on here.
Comes Bissa for South Africa straight away.
A quick pinch.
Mustard.
To the line.
For the spring box.
I'm the flare.
Acki.
Comes in down to the halfway line.
For the Irish side.
Can I ever again?
Takes some kicks off.
Feliciae comes in.
Wants the pull.
Stays with the ball.
The men in green.
Use it.
Six and two.
The right hand side.
He lets his forwards attack a bit more.
Panely.
South Africa.
He's...
One up.
From inside.
He's off.
Thuff to Clack.
As if the upwork.
It's come bouncing back.
And flying up there was Chesson Colby for South Africa.
Oh!
Somehow the spring box haven't.
Kill goes to the right.
And the numbers there.
This may work out better for the spring box if they do score a try.
Just for Vissa.
Crunches forward.
The Clack finds.
It's a bad.
Who's picked up?
Right down.
That is a...
Clack real for Central Media.
Yeah, that's a bad.
That's been thrown down to the party.
Crouch.
Fine.
See.
Ever up.
Bonson.
Leasing Clapsing.
Ever up.
And Bonyx for South Africa with four of their Bonsquad members on the field.
The Elendi beautiful ball on the outside.
South Africa will power over.
Chesson and Colby.
What's the drive?
Forget low cheating.
He's electric 24, seven.
And it was Marnie La Barca.
They delivered the goods.
Chesson and Colby in the Olympian.
He's magic in open space.
And there was plenty of it down on this touch line.
The only easier run into.
The Clack ticks five seconds to take the kick.
Just pulls it to the left-hand side.
And the same's continuing here.
This is pull beat.
Number one and two side in the world.
It's penalty to Ireland.
Sexton is a smooth operator.
And Ireland go back in the lead.
Correct.
And half.
The hard minute rugby.
The forwards.
And the spring blocks.
Call one back.
That's so straight.
Pushing straight.
Oh, they're not saying straight.
The red number's getting very low.
As Marnie La Barca looks on.
Unsuccessful.
It has come onto the field.
The big changes are both sides.
Who can finish off strongly?
It comes.
Love's eating green millies.
He's not scared.
They can't wait.
First touch for June Parie.
The oldest test.
Different touch into the advocate history.
This is the 31 year old.
Banks it downfield.
And Mrs.
F1.
Here we go.
As the world watches.
Penelope Ireland.
the island. You can hear the
roar. Point lead.
Paulie has his name in the box.
It's 13 points to right.
Island leads South Africa.
Moving towards the Chalant.
Yeah, Lenny's in there as well.
Todd Burn, the Irish defender on the side.
It's defended.
It's the public.
Where is it?
The other trying to dig us out.
Is that as they come out?
Island.
I've done it.
Another one team in the world.
Irish hours are smiling tonight.
They've taken one step closer to the rugby world cup
dream.
They're beating the spring box.
It's been an extraordinary evening in Paris.
They'll be tears.
They'll be celebrations.
80,000 fans.
Yeah, millions around the world.